{
    "Questions": [
       
            {
				"qid": 1,
                "question": "ASP.NET was developed by",
                "options": [
                    "IBM",
                    "Google",
                    "Microsoft",
                    "Apple"
                ],
                "answer": "Microsoft"
            },
            
            {
			  "qid" : 2,
              "question": "The file extension an ASP.NET web form is -",
              "options": [
                    ".html",
                    ".cs",
                    ".aspx",
                    ".js"
                
                ],
                "answer": ".aspx"
            },
            
            {
			  "qid" : 3,
              "question": "The term for the pages that depend upon a master page is called-",
              "options": [
                    "Master pages",
                    "Content pages",
                    "Web pages",
                    "My pages"
                
                ],
                "answer": "Content pages"
            },
            
            {
			  "qid" : 4,
              "question": "Application_Start event is available in ________ .",
              "options": [
                    "Web.config",
                    "Local.asax",
                    "Global.asax",
                    "Start.aspx"
                
                ],
                "answer": "Global.asax"
            },
            
            {
              "qid" : 5,
			  "question": "____________ is not an ASP.NET page event.",
              "options": [
                    "Init",
                    "Load",
                    "Import",
                    "All of the above"
                
                ],
                "answer": "Import"
            },
            
            {
			   "qid" : 6,
              "question": "ASP.NET was first released in",
              "options": [
                    "Jan 2004",
                    "Feb 2002",
                    "Jan 2001",
                    "Jan 2002"
                
                ],
                "answer": "Jan 2002"
            },
            
            
            {
              "qid" : 7,
			  "question": "Which of the following is the first event of the ASP.NET page, when the user requests a web page?",
              "options": [
                    "Init",
                    "Load",
                    "PreInit",
                    "PreLoad"
                
                ],
                "answer": "PreInit"
            },
            
           {
              "qid" : 8,
			  "question": "True or False, Boolean is the DataType return in IsPostback property.",
              "options": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                
                ],
                "answer": "True"
            },
            
           {
              "qid" : 9,
			  "question": " _________________ is the code mixed with the HTML and asp controls called?",
              "options": [
                    "Inline Code",
                    "Bar Code",
                    "Both a & b"
                  
                
                ],
                "answer": "Inline Code"
            },
            
          {
              "qid" : 10,
			  "question": "True or False, We are not using a server when we run our .aspx projects",
              "options": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                
                ],
                "answer": "False"
            }
            
            
        ]
        
    
}